### **Profile**

I am friendly, hardworking, reliable and have a personal passion for Computers and Technology. I have recently passed the Microsoft MTA 98-361 Software Development Fundamentals C# exam through self-study and following this I was selected to attend the Generation Tech Talent Accelerator 6 week coding boot camp where I received the opportunity to work in different teams, learn more in depth coding skills and completed two projects. I am keen to continue learning new skills whilst seeking a job opportunity in industry as a Software Developer/Engineer. I am really enjoying innovating and designing solutions using code and work hard to perfect the outcome of my work.

I take pride that in my previous career my clients were always happy with my solutions for them and continually returned. I feel I am a quick learner and my enthusiasm and desire to learn new skills and techniques from those around me I would say are my best attributes.

With over 5 years experience as a Hair Stylist in fast paced salons, hairdressing has enhanced my communication skills and ability to stay calm in stressful situations. Client satisfaction is key to me, always ensuring I have a mutual understanding with my clients of what they desire and what to expect from me. I hope to make use of some of these skills as I embark on my future career in Software Development and Engineering.

## Education

#### Sep 28th 2020 -**Generation Tech Talent Accelerator bootcamp**

Nov 7th 2020 HTML, CSS, JavaScript, DOM manipulation, Bootstrap, Flex Box, Git & GitHub, Binary, Soft Skills

#### Feb 2020 -Microsoft MTA 98-361 Software Development Fundamentals C# exam

June 2020 C#, SQL, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, ASP.NET

#### 2012 - 2014Hertford Regional College (Ware)

Ladies Hairdressing VRQ Level 3 (equivalent to 3 A levels)

Men's Barbering VRQ Level 3 Ladies Hairdressing VRQ Level 2 VRQ Level 1 & 2 Men's Barbering

Functional Skills English Grade/Level 2 (equivalent to C-A\*)

#### 2009-2012: Monk's Walk School, Welwyn Garden City

**GCSE and GCSE Equivalent Qualifications** 

Mathematics (C), English language (D) English Media Studies (C), Biology(C), Chemistry(C), Physics(C) ICT level2 Merit, ICT Media level 2 PDMM, D&T Food Technology (D), Religious Studies (D).

### **Work Experience**

#### Rush Hackney - Director Hair Stylist 2019-20

 Hair Styling for Men, Women & Children Administrative duties

#### 2012-19 Katrina Hair Salon London NW2 - Stylist

Hair Styling for Men. Women & Children

© Cutting, Colouring/Highlighting, Blow drying, Perming, Hair up

Managerial responsibilities Administrative duties ⊕ Regulating Stock Taking client calls Handling Finances Handling client disputes

Opening and closing the shop Managing employee schedules

# **Key Skills**

- Mnowledge of a variety of programming languages including C#, HTML, CSS, JavaScript and SQL.
- Knowledge of Visual Studio.
- © Able to work individually without direct supervision and also as part of a team.

### **Achievements**

Other

2014: Ladies' Hairdressing VRQ Level 3 student of the year.

2014: Achievement in functional Skills.

### 2014: Provisional Driver's License

2016: Driving Licence

## **Interests and Hobbies**

# Elena Georgiou

Painting, Listening to music, Skating, Computers & Gaming, Puzzles, Cooking/baking, Movies